

#### **DETAILS**

Ranibazar-190, Ghoramara, Boalia, Rajshahi-6100.

+8801718822679

mirhaiderhimel@gmail.com

Nationality: Bangladeshi

Date/Place of Birth:

02/05/1996, Rajshahi

NID No: 780 070 7395

#### **SKILLS**

Communication Skill

Time Management

**Passion for Learning** 

Ability to multi-task

**Problem Solving** 

**Analytical Thinking** 

# **MIR HAIDER**

### **Career Objective**

Aiming to join an established organization like your organization where I can add value through my skills in financial analysis, business development and corporate finance, which can help me learn new skills and values creative problem solving skills and analytical thinking.

# **Career Summary**

I worked at Mutual Trust Bank Ltd. as a Call Center Executive with overall banking practices. Except that, I did my work at IT Craft as a Marketing Executive Officer and I did my internship at Southeast Bank Ltd. for three months. I worked also at MetLife Bangladesh as a Financial Associate. So I do believe in teamwork as it contributes efficiently towards success.

## **Academic Qualifications**

#### **Master of Business Administration (MBA)**

Institute : University of Rajshahi.

Concentration : Finance

Result : CGPA-3.75 (Out of 4.00)

Course Duration : 1Year Passing Year : 2019

### **Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)**

Institute : North Bengal International University, Rajshahi.

Concentration : Finance

Result : CGPA-3.92 (Out of 4.00)

Course Duration : 4-Year Passing Year : 2018

#### **Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)**

Institute : Varendra College, Rajshahi.

Group : Science

GPA : 3.50 (Out of 5.00)

Passing Year : 2013

#### Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

Institute : Masjid Mission Academy School & College.

Group : Science

GPA : 4.38 (Out of 5.00)

Passing Year : 2011

# **Work Experiences**

Call Center Executive (May 2022-Sep 2023)

#### Mutual Trust Bank PLC. (MTB Tower Branch, Dhaka)

- Identify customer needs, gives precise information with clarification and provide appropriate solutions for ensuring utmost customer satisfaction.
- Executing customer request, resolving complaint and refer unresolved customer grievances to designated persons.
- Obtain and examine all relevant information with a view to assessing the validity of complaints.

#### **Marketing Executive Officer**

(Feb 2020- Mar 2021)

#### IT Craft (Station Road, Rajshahi)

- (a) Developed and executed marketing programs and general business solutions resulting in increased company exposure and elevated sales numbers.
- (b) Worked with communication team to drive internal promotion of company programs, initiatives and mission.
- (c) Established targets for social media platforms to reflect business objectives.

#### LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

Bangla: Native

**English: Professional** 

#### **SOFTWARE**

- Skills on CMS (Card Management System),
   CBS(Core Banking System),
   TWCMS (Transware Card Management System), VOC.
- Office Application(MS word, PowerPoint, Excel)
- Windows (XP/ 7,8,10)
- Adobe Photoshop

# **Internship Experience**

Intern (May 2018- Aug2018)

### Southeast Bank Limited, Rajshahi Branch

- (a) Assisted customers with setting up or opening or closing accounts, completing loan applications and signing up for new services.
- (b) Responsibility was to take check orders and keep detailed records of transactions.
- (c) Established new accounts for high net worth individuals and serviced existing accounts to maximize revenue.

# **Computer Proficiency**

#### **MS Office Application**

(Jan 2017-Jun 2017)

#### Campus Institute of Science & Technology, Rajshahi

- (a) Expertise knowledge of using Windows Operating System and of accessing internet.
- **(b)** Eligible in MS Office Word, MS Excel, Power Point and others basic computer programs.

### **Personal Informations**

Name : Mir Haider
Father's Name : Mir Asir Uddin
Mother's Name : Hamida Begum
Date of Birth : 02/05/1996

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Unmarried

Present Address : Ranibazar-190, Ghoramara, Boalia, Rajshahi-6100. Permanent Address : Ranibazar-190, Ghoramara, Boalia, Rajshahi-6100.

Religion : Islam

Nationality : Bangladeshi National Id : 780 070 7395

# **Training and Workshops**

Training Title: Business Etiquettes and Call Center Customer Service Soft Skills
 Topic Covered: Overall Banking Products and Services and Soft skills

(CBS, CTI, CMS, TWCMS)

**HOBBIES** 

Computing

Travelling

Learning a new skill

Playing team sports

Solving puzzles

Institute: MTB Training Institute

Training Duration and Year: 2 month (2022)

Training Title: Direct Selling and Marketing Banking Products.

Topic Covered: To sell banking products (All sorts of credit card sales)

Institute: United Commercial Bank PLC Training Duration and Year: 1 month (2021)

• Training Title : Sales Policy-FA(2020)

Topic Covered: Policy of sales of insurance and financial associate's duties.

Institute: MetLife Bangladesh

Training Duration and Year: 1 month (2020)

### **Extra-Curricular Activities**

1. Brand Promoter of Square-'Chopstick Noodles' (Mar2022)

• Demonstrated and provided information on Chopstick noodles for Square.

2. Surveyor of 'Keya Cosmetics Limited'

(Nov2015)

• Surveyed the market on "Keya cosmetics and toiletries products" for the development of new products in the existing product line.

**3.** Participated on "Debate Competition (Interdepartmental)"- arranged by North Bengal International University, Rajshahi.

### **References**

Prof. Dr. M. Amzad Hossain Professor

Department of Finance University of Rajshahi.

Mobile: +8801712061028

E-mail: mdahossain@ru.ac.bd

Noor Mohammad Shafi Kamal

**Head of Digital Banking and Innovation** 

Commercial Bank of Ceylon

Hadi Tower, Road: 50, Gulshan-2, Dhaka.

Mobile: +8801712006950

E-mail: m.shafi.kamal@gmail.com

# **Declaration**

I, the undersigned, certify to the best of my knowledge and belief that the mentioned data are correct with describe my qualification and me.

Mirz Haiderz

Mir Haider